<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">TooLearn</string>
  <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
  <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
  <string name="qbrules1">1. A certain time limit is given for every question. Failure to respond to a question within the given time frame will result to a zerocpoint mark for that specific question.</string>
  <string name="qbrules2">2. For a Multiple Choice Format,there will be four choices for each question given. Users should choose the best answer which  corresponds to the question.</string>
  <string name="qbrules3">3. For a True or False Format, there will only two choices it will be Correct or Incorrect answer.</string>
  <string name="qbrules4">4. For a Short Answer Format, participants are provided with a text box to input their answer to the question. Misspelled answers will be marked incorrect.</string>
  <string name="qbrules5">5. Feedbacks regarding the correctness of answers are presented after answering each question. Once a player answers a question incorrectly or not the best, the correct or best answer will be flashed on the screen.</string>
  <string name="qbrules6">6. Additional points will be given to participants who can give the correct answer for each question first. Automatic merits depend on the facilitators preference.</string>
  <string name="pprules1">1. A particular picture is divided into nine equal parts. Puzzle parts will remain blurred unless the question for that part is already answered.</string>
  <string name="pprules2">2. Each piece of the puzzle has a a corresponding points. Players can gain points if they able to provide the correct or best answer.</string>
  <string name="pprules3">3. The first player to solve the whole picture will be given bonus point.</string>
  <string name="pprules4">4. For a Multiple Choice Format,there will be four choices for each question given. Users should choose the best answer which  corresponds to the question.</string>
  <string name="pprules5">5. For a True or False Format, there will only two choices it will be Correct or Incorrect answer.</string>
  <string name="pprules6">6. For a Short Answer Format, participants are provided with a text box to input their answer to the question. Misspelled answers will be marked incorrect.</string>
  <string name="pprules7">7. Additional points will be given to participants who can give the correct or best answer for each question first. Automatic merits depends on the facilitators preference.</string>
  <string name="pprules8">8. A certain time limit is given for every question. Failure to respond to a question within the given time frame will result to a zero point mark for that specific question.</string>
  <string name="pprules9">9. Feedbacks regarding the correctness of answers are presented after answering each question. Once a player answers a question incorrectly or not the best, the correct or best answer will be flashed on the screen.</string>
</resources>